Wash your hands and don PPE.
equipment
You will need gauze, cotton wool, cardboard, pencil, cup, sticky paper and scissors.
cotton
For the eye pad, spread a cotton wool ball into an oval shape about 5 to 6 centimetres wide.
gauze
Fold the gauze around the cotton wool.
pad-tape
Tape at the open end.
trim
Trim the edges of the gauze to the shape of the cotton wool.
finished-pad
This is your eye pad.
cardboard
For the shield, find some clean cardboard. Reusing medical packaging works well.
draw
Using a cup as a template, draw a circle with a diameter of about 8 centimetres.
cut
Cut out the circle.
slit
Then make a cut from the edge to the centre.
cone
Curve the card into a cone and secure with sticky tape.
finished-shield
This is your eye shield.